Let's get on to our last stretch.
It is a good stretch for the shoulders.
So you are going to start by facing the wall like you are in trouble, just kidding.
You are going to reach your right arm straight up in the air just like Alex has here.
From here you are going to open out to the side so you are going to make sure that your shoulder is completely in line.
You don't want it above or below but straight in line with that shoulder and then you are going to slowly start to turn your body out to the left side.
As you are pressing the shoulder down into the wall and you don't have to turn the shoulder very much here but it is a good shoulder to open up that chest.
Good, take a deep inhale here and try to twist a little bit more as you straighten the body all the way, good and then come back to center.
Face the wall again and make sure you lift the arms straight up and then lower it right back down to your side.
We are going to switch to the left arms and lift your left arms straight up in the air.
Make sure you stay towards the center as you open the arms out to the side and you don't get out of the stretch the wrong way.
From here you are going to twist that shoulder and face towards your other side.
Take a deep breath on the inhale and as you exhale I want you to twist and press that shoulder into that wall.
Get both shoulders even and away from your ears and then slowly twist the waist right back facing that wall.
Lift your left arm straight up in the air and slowly float it all the way back down.
You can step away from the wall and you are done.
That was the shoulder wall stretch.
I want to thank you guys for watching today.
I put these stretches together so that you can start to learn about pilates and your body so make sure that you guys get in there and make sure that you stretch correctly.
I want to thank Alex and Carrie today and Base Pilates for having me here.
Make sure to see my other videos and I'll see you guys soon.
Thanks for watching.